<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SIG on SRMA SIG</title>
    <link>https://www.srmasig.org/tags/sig/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SIG on SRMA SIG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.srmasig.org/tags/sig/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Call for SIG Officer Nominations</title>
      <link>https://www.srmasig.org/posts/business/call-for-nominations-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.srmasig.org/posts/business/call-for-nominations-2025/</guid>
      <description>Our Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis SIG is seeking new officers for the leadership team, with terms starting after the end of the 2025 convention next April. We welcome nominations (including self-nominations!) for any of the following positions:
Program Chair – organizes and manages the proposal review process and assembles the SIG’s program for the annual convention.Secretary – reports on SIG activities, including the annual business meeting, and leads communications with SIG members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Officers</title>
      <link>https://www.srmasig.org/posts/business/new_officers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.srmasig.org/posts/business/new_officers/</guid>
      <description>This past January, AERA held its annual elections, which included elections for several officer positions in our SIG. Results were announced recently Officers for the 2023-2025 term will be:
Program co-chairs: Carlton Fong (Texas State University) and Derek Rodgers (University of Iowa)Secretary: Amanda Neitzel (Johns Hopkins University)Treasurer: Megha Joshi (American Institutes of Research)Graduate Student Representative-at-Large: Qiyang Zhang (Johns Hopkins University)SIG Chair: James Pustejovsky (University of Wisconsin – Madison)I look forward to working with our new officers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for SIG Officer Nominations</title>
      <link>https://www.srmasig.org/posts/business/call-for-nominations-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.srmasig.org/posts/business/call-for-nominations-2023/</guid>
      <description>Our SIG will soon be holding elections for new officers. The terms of the current officers run through April, 2023, and all five positions on the leadership team will be up for election. In order to hold elections, we need candidates! We are now soliciting nominations (including self-nominations!) for all positions. If you are interested in running for a position, please contact SIG chair James Pustejovsky, no later than October 28th, 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
